kingarthurflour.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | King Arthur Flour

  * Bakery Café + Store
  * Baking School
  * Bakery Flour Sales
  * Contact

  * Shop
  * Recipes
  * Learn
  * Our Story
  * Our Products

We respect your privacy, and value the confidence you've shown in us by choosing to shop via our site.

King Arthur's Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected anytime you interact with us, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase King Arthur products, or when you call our sales or customer service personnel.

##### Why we collect personal information

In order to be a premier resource for quality baking products, and to provide the knowledge and inspiration to use them, we record a variety of information from your visit here. We use this information to support our mission to “share the pure joy of baking” and to ensure continuous improvement of our products, service, and marketing efforts. It's our intent to ensure this Privacy Promise is honest, complete, clear, and current, so as things evolve or questions arise we will periodically review and update this promise to you.

##### What we collect

We record the address of the website you came from before visiting us, and any terms you may have searched on to arrive at our site. We also record the pages you viewed on our site. We do this so we can help future visitors find what they're looking for more easily, and to improve the navigability of our site. 

If you join The Baking Circle or participate in any online survey we may offer, we record your e-mail address and the information you provide us on the questionnaire. We use your e-mail address to contact you with special offers, recipes, and news about King Arthur Flour that may be of interest to you. We use summaries of the data collected from the questionnaire to help us improve the service we offer you.

If you place a catalogue request, order online, or contact us via e-mail, we record your e-mail and postal address so we're able to respond to you in the quickest, most effective way possible. You may receive periodic contacts from us via mail or e-mail with information on new products, services, or upcoming events. We also sometimes rent or exchange our list of postal addresses with other marketers with whom we share similar customers, and whose products and offer we feel could benefit you. If you'd prefer we didn't share your name and postal address, please let us know by contacting us. 

##### Your email address

Each e-mail promotion, recipe, or update you receive from us will include instructions on how you can remove your e-mail address from our list. We sometimes provide your email address—although not your name, physical address, or other personal information—to companies that advise us on broad customer trends. We will also disclose your email address when/if required to do so under applicable law.

We have the opportunity to use your e-mail address to help our environment by reducing the number of catalogues that we and others put in the mail. If you'd like to reduce the quantity of catalogues you receive from us, please let us know by contacting us.

##### Integrity of your personal information

If you place an order online and we request your customer number or key code from the catalogue you received in the mail, this is only for purposes of extending to you any promotional offers associated with that catalogue, and for evaluating where we can cut back the number of catalogues mailed. The credit card information that’s required to complete your order is strictly confidential, and will never be used for anything other than processing your order or for future returns on that order.

##### Cookies

Certain features and services we offer on our website may require we place a “cookie” (a computer one, not a flour and sugar one!) on your computer. If this is the case, we'll make it clear to you at the time you join or register for that feature and service, and let you know why the “cookie” is needed and what it'll be used for.

##### Privacy questions

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us.
